Hey!
Something's coming this way!
I don't know who you are, but
you're definitely not normal!
Hold it, Riff!
Stop it!
I'm gonna make short work of you!
Another playing card?
Master Joestar, welcome to our abode.
We've been expecting you.
How rude of me.
I am the butler of this
mansion you may call me Darby.
Darby huh yes I am the younger
Darby it might interest you
to know the Darby whom you
defeated upon your arrival was
my older brother so there
isn't just one so loud in the
Darby family so I take it you're
here to avenge your brother's
defeat no not at all such a thing
is beneath me i would have assumed
my brother would share his motto
with you it is the deceived not
the deceiver who holds the blame i
too live by this adage my brother
lost so he is the wrongdoer i harbor
no ill will toward any of you?
My brother is my brother and I
am me, two different individuals.
You see, my brother and I
were born ten years apart,
and while I did look up to
him to a certain extent,
he and I are of different generations.
My brother tried to win via
old-fashioned deception,
but this method is only useful against
those who are outdated or inexperienced.
Master Dio realized
this sad truth as well,
which is why he kept me by his
side as his personal butler.
Hmm?
Forgive me, is something the matter?
Here is my offer to you.
If you wish to fight me, then I invite
you to enter our manor. Stay on guard.
He's even more conniving than his brother.
There's no time for games.
Take us to Dio right now.
Dojuro, stay on your guard!
He's up to something!
Darby Younger, his stand hailing
from the Egyptian pantheon is Atum.
Hey, guys, he just brought out his stand.
It's been a while since we've seen one.
Indeed, his stand is
physically showing itself.
I'll let you decide who
shall be my first opponent.
As if we'd listen to you.
Jotaro, take this weirdo down.
Let's see.
I'll wager that Star
Platinum's first attack will...
Be with his left arm.
Oh, and it'll be a punch.
How much would you care to bet?
Forget this.
Which arm doesn't matter?
One punch will finish it. Get him!
Let him have it already, Jotaro!
Hoorah!
What?
He was able to dodge it!
His speed is insane! Impossible!
Well, that's a bit of bad luck.
Regrettably, it appears as
though I've lost the bet.
Like my brother, I also enjoy a round of
gambling, but luck is never on my side.
Allow me to take you to a
wonderful world to apologize.
What? A bit? Damn it!
It was all subterfuge! Jotaro!
He's falling into the abyss!
We have to get him out of there!
Have it your way.
The more the merrier and all that Mr.
Joestar cocky we know it's too
dangerous for us to follow.
Can you hear me if you
don't hear from us in 10
minutes Torch the mansion
do you understand me?
Burn it to the ground Mr.
Joestar
Hmm.
Is this an illusion?
Are we still above ground?
Or did he pull us under?
If this stuff is really an
illusion, they've got watered down.
This stuff feels so real.
What the hell is this guy
trying to accomplish here?
Old man, Kakyoin.
See if you can figure out his ability.
His stand.
It knew without a doubt that I
would throw a right-handed punch.
Do you know why?
Hmm.
If we can't figure it out soon,
we're gonna lose, no doubt.
Would you care to wet your whistle?
They're real, and I assure
you they're not poisoned.
Cross my heart and hope to die.
Just answer this.
Are we inside the mansion?
Yes, of course.
Where in the mansion are we?
I can't tell you that. The basement?
Perhaps.
Hmm.
Is this illusion the
work of a stand's power?
Yes, it is.
Is all this the doing of your stand?
No, it isn't.
Is it Dio's stand?
Whose stand, then?
I would rather not reveal that.
The Speedwagon Foundation has reported
there are two to three more stand users.
Is that accurate?
I'd rather not reveal that either.
Well, you're about as helpful
as a cramp in a relay race.
If it means so much, I could lie to you.
But unlike my dearly defeated brother, I
prefer not to resort to petty trickery.
Let me make sure I've got this straight.
You're saying if we don't defeat you,
we won't be able to get
back to the real world?
Exactly right!
You've pieced it together, good sir!
That obnoxious gentlemanly demeanor is
beginning to wear thin on my nerves.
You seem to be forgetting
that it's three against one.
We're short on time, so you'll have to
deal with all of us attacking at once.
Come now, friends.
You should take a load off.
Feast your eyes on what
I have to show you.
Say hello to my collection.
Your collection?
Much like my brother, I'm what you
might call a humble collector of sorts.
My, thinking about it,
all collectors must yearn to share their
treasures for that moment of praise.
He's out of his mind.
Why dolls?
What could he possibly
be doing with these toys?
I don't think I want to know.
Remember, this guy is Darby's brother, so
I'm guessing those aren't ordinary dolls.
Darby, talk to me, please
talk, why won't you talk to me,
Darby, talk to me,
oh my
god?
They're alive, how is that even
possible, bastard, you took their souls?
Obviously as making dolls is my hobby,
but of course ordinary doll makers cannot
imbue their handiwork with human souls.
I suppose I may be giving too much
away, but that's my Stan's ability.
Comparatively my brother's collection of
simple coins made of souls
is rather uninspired.
With my collection you can play
dress up and have actual chats.
Let me show you
This little showstopper is named Sonia.
She can wax poetic about her passionate
love stories Such exquisite skin.
Anyone would be proud to own her. Dr.
Elliot is a serial killer
with a victim count of eight.
He'll tell you all about the
patients he's exterminated.
I made the glasses and stethoscope myself.
Oh, I nearly forgot.
I'd like for you to meet Tatsuhiko.
This one's a game expert from Japan.
This brilliant young man was a
formidable opponent with an IQ of 190.
Let me tell you, it wasn't easy beating
this little guy and stealing his soul.
You're just as messed up in
the head as your brother.
Actually, you're more sadistic
than your brother ever was.
I hate to see what your parents were like.
I'm out of patience with
this sociopath's puppet show.
He makes me sick.
By the way, I'm fairly certain you
learned this when you fought my brother,
but the human soul can be
a rather mysterious entity.
The moment a person admits defeat,
their inner spirit dies, and the
soul loses almost all vitality.
At that moment, I have the power
to rip the soul from the body.
And that's the fundamental
mechanism of our stance!
I've heard enough!
Show and tell is over!
We're gonna beat you to a bloody
pulp and get the hell out of here!
But first, listen to what I have to say.
Surely, the fact that you're under my
control hasn't escaped your notice.
Jotaro,
as I recall,
you were quite shocked when I knew exactly
which arm you were
going to attack me with.
And from where I'm standing, it seems
you still haven't figured it out.
You were shaken by my prowess and I was
able to give your soul a little love tag.
What do you think I did
when I touched your soul?
What the...
The hell did you do to his arm?
I've done nothing but embed a
tomb's hand inside Jotaro's soul.
I could crush your
right arm with a thought
and in doing so make
Master Dio very happy.
But if I did,
I wouldn't be able to
defend myself against
Kakyoin and Joseph and
would most certainly perish.
Now, we wouldn't want that to
happen, would we, gentlemen?
So here's a suggestion.
Everyone, let's play a game
with our souls as collateral.
What?
If you defeat me, I solemnly
swear to release Jotaro's arm.
Ah, good grief.
So according to you, I'm
already under your control.
Well, I have news for you, Darby.
You're gonna regret picking a
fight with me and my friends.
Let's end this!
Yes, yes, your righteous
anger is all well and good.
But I'd rather hear you say the
words, I'll bet my soul on this game.
By the way, I have another
request if you'd indulge me.
Kakyoin, you shall be my first opponent.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Your fight is with me, buddy, so don't
try and pass the buck to Kakyoin.
You and Mr.
Joestar are family.
But Kakyoin is decidedly not.
I'd prefer Kakyoin not back
out of our arrangement.
And attack me with his stand after
I've taken both of your souls?
due to lack of familial attachment.
I'm sick of this arrogant prick.
He thinks this challenge is going
to be a walk in the park for him.
Very well.
If that's what you want,
then I will be your opponent.
Say what? Kaku-ing!
It's okay.
I'm really not too concerned.
I've probably played more video
games than anyone else here.
I officially accept your challenge
and choose F Mega as our game.
And I'll wager my soul!
And I'll wager my soul.
Very good.
Kick Wing, don't!
There's no need for you
to take this guy on first.
I have to do this.
We still don't have a
grasp on that spirit hand.
It could hinder your game-playing ability.
Darby,
do I have your guarantee
that you'll release
Jotaro from your stand's
power if you lose the game?
Huh?
The TV console and game
cartridges are all good.
As far as I can tell, this
is just an ordinary setup.
I keep trying to tell you that
I'm not a cheater like my brother.
If you're ready, let's begin.
Let's do it!
F-Mega!
Select your car!
Go ahead and select your vehicle.
Right.
So you've decided to go with number 28.
I suppose I'll be number 15,
as my birthday is January 5th.
We can begin at your leisure.
Enough with the courtesy.
Start the game already.
Race starts in five!
He's button-mashing the
accelerator at an incredible speed!
He's going for a Tribe start! Three!
Damn!
I don't have time to try the Sing tactic.
He'll take the lead.
What am I going to do now?
One!
Start!
What he just cut me off as
long as I'm in the lead he
can't beat me and I've made
it impossible for him to
pass it's unfortunate I
know but the simple truth is
I never make a mistake during a
Victory will be mine, Kakyoin!
What the...
Kakyoin, you've played this
game before, haven't you?
I'd rather not reveal that. Yes!
This is your chance, Kakyoin!
Get your machine back on course and
start kicking this bastard's ass!
That technique!
One doesn't simply get those skills
by playing video games! Damn it all!
I never could have
imagined that someone as
measured as Kakyoin would
make such a bold move!
Yeah, that's the way to do it!
Neck and neck! No.
Look carefully, old man.
Kakyoin's at the edge.
When it comes to those turns,
he's at a major disadvantage.
355 kmh, now it's 358, and now 360,
three seconds until the first turn,
but there's no way I can
make it going this fast,
I'm entering the turn at full speed,
two, one!
You seeing this?
Those two are hitting the
turns the exact same way.
It's too close to call.
You've intrigued me, Kakyoin.
With your soul on the line,
you've conquered your fear and become
the picture of unwavering resolve.
I dare say you'll make a worthy
addition to my collection.
All that's left is for me to win.
Kakyoin thought to himself.
So, I've conquered my fears, have I?
Why, thank you.
It's been a long road.
Six months ago, I had the unfortunate
experience of meeting your master, Dio.
I was terrified when he implanted
one of his flesh buds in my brain.
My memories of that day
are as clear as ever.
I remember the horror I felt in
my soul as I faced that monster.
My legs wouldn't move.
Every hair on my body stood on end.
It's like I was frozen.
That's when I realized it.
I was helpless, completely at his mercy.
The mere sight of Dio was enough
to turn my own body against itself.
My stomach was in knots.
I was so close to vomiting, I could
taste bile in the back of my throat.
Dio gazed down at me, and, as if
tenderly calming a frightened child,
he said, Easy, Kakyoin.
There is nothing for you to be afraid of.
Let's be friends, shall we?
I still curse myself.
I heard his words and...
And I felt all of my anxiety melt away.
I was completely and utterly relieved.
I thought, I still have a chance to live.
It was humiliating.
I'll never forgive him for what he did.
And I'll never forgive myself for
submitting to that bastard's will.
My weakness will forever
be my greatest failure.
Jotaro saved me from that hell, which
is why I've come on this journey.
I will never again allow
myself to be such a coward.
And that, Darby, is why I'm able to fight
you even with my very soul on the line.
Three, two, one!
They're neck and neck again!
Rounding the third corner!
That is why, on this day, I vow that I,
Noriyaki Kakyoin, will never be
controlled by my fears again!
My word is my bond! All right!
It's the fifth corner!
They're back in sync!
Look, they're turning at the same speed!
Damn you, Kakyoin! Damn you!
The sixth corner is coming up fast!
If I'm not mistaken, the speed
tunnel comes right after turn six.
If you enter that tunnel,
you're granted a boost that can
double your max speed to 850 kmh.
I have to make sure I get to that tunnel.
But the thing is, the tunnel's
only wide enough for one car.
This isn't good.
If they try to enter the tunnel side
by side, one of them is going to crash.
It's the sixth turn, and
they're still neck and neck.
There it is.
I see the tunnel.
Kakyoin, push him out of the way.
Haven't you realized it yet, Kakyoin?
You don't have the power to push me aside.
If you don't believe me, why not
glance at your handy-dandy power meter?
Hmm?
Hakui, you have less power than he does!
You used up your power
when you spun around and
blocked me back at the
beginning of the race.
That wasn't the best move on your part.
I bet you're regretting that decision now!
So close.
Two seconds till the tunnel.
You're gonna crash!
You can let this fool have the lead.
Get behind him to avoid
crashing right now!
I can't do that.
If he makes it to the tunnel first, my
chances of winning go to absolute zero.
One second left till victory.
Cocaine!
My god!
He's got the car up on two wheels!
How absurd you're riding the tunnel walls.
Yes you've got this in the
bed Kakyoin just hang on.
A little bit further and
victory will be ours.
Now push him aside.
Quiet I'm concentrating.
Watch out he's slamming you.
It makes no difference to
me if I lose some power.
My only concern is getting around
that turn faster than Kakyoin.
Even if it's only by a
hundredth of a second.
Just one one-thousandth
of a millimeter ahead.
No radar!
Hey, what's going on here?
Can't see the cars!
From here on out, we have to get through
the tunnel in almost absolute darkness.
What?
The problem is my radar
will be completely useless.
And worse,
there are eight turns, a landmine,
and a cannon attack waiting to
put us through our paces up ahead.
This area will remain
dark until we make it out.
One mistake and I'll slam into the wall.
But fortunately for us, I already
know exactly where each turn is.
Darby knows, too.
The cars are beginning to turn.
What's happening, Jotaro?
I can't tell who's ahead or where
they are in that blasted tunnel.
Three, two, and one. Cannon attack!
Did you see that?
For a second there, the
blast lit up the cars.
Yeah, I can see that cocky-o-ing
is running slightly behind.
Here we go.
They're about to exit the tunnel.
Oh, dammit!
Darby was able to take the lead!
He's ahead by a full car lane!
Looks like I win!
Thank you.
I'd never be foolish enough
to let my guard down.
The weaker car loses in a collision.
This all belongs to me.
We should be kicking this guy's ass.
We're playing baseball.
You can't just back out of this.
This is the worst pep
talk I've ever heard.
He's getting even worse.